beyondunreal.com 2003-04-01

# BeyondUnreal's HelpDesk powered by DeskPRO.com

**Answer:**  
BeyondUnreal Privacy Statement 

BeyondUnreal, Inc. (BeyondUnreal) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information and to track user patterns of different areas and themes within the site. 

Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of our members and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

The bulletin board uses cookies to store the last time you logged in, your username and password, and your preferred "topic view", if you set it in preferences. These cookies are stored on your browser. 

Advertising 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Member Registration Forms, Surveys and Newsletters. 

Our site's registration forms require users to give us contact information (name, email). 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. 

All information gathered from the registration form, email newsletter subscription form and survey form is used by BeyondUnreal personnel for communication purposes. 

We do not divulge any personally identifying information to any 3rd party organisation. 

External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. BeyondUnreal is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Forums and Message Boards 

This site makes forums and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Considering the real-time nature of the bulletin board, it is impossible for us to review messages or confirm the validity of information posted. Please remember that we do not actively monitor the contents of posted messages and are not responsible for any messages posted. We do not vouch for or warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any message, and are not responsible for the contents of any message. The messages express the views of the author of the message, not necessarily the views of BeyondUnreal or any entity associated with BeyondUnreal. Any user who feels that a posted message is objectionable is encouraged to contact us immediately by email. We have the ability to remove objectionable messages and we will make every effort to do so, within a reasonable time frame, if we determine that removal is necessary. This is a manual process, however, so please realize that we may not be able to remove or edit particular messages immediately. 

You agree, through your use of the forums, that you will not use them to post any material which is knowingly false and/or defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, vulgar, hateful, harassing, obscene, profane, sexually oriented, threatening, invasive of a person's privacy, or otherwise violative of any law. You agree not to post any copyrighted material unless the copyright is owned by you or by BeyondUnreal. 

Although BeyondUnreal does not and cannot review the messages posted and is not responsible for the content of any of these messages, we reserve the right to delete any message for any or no reason whatsoever. You remain solely responsible for the content of your messages, and you agree to indemnify and hold harmless BeyondUnreal, Jelsoft Enterprises Lmt. (the makers of the bulletin board software), and their agents with respect to any claim based upon transmission of your message(s). We at BeyondUnreal also reserve the right to reveal your identity (or whatever information we know about you) in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any message posted by you. 

Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
